T-To the festival?!
Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Well... Yeah...
I always go with you guys, so I wanted
to let you know ahead of time.
Wow, that's awesome. I'm so jealous!
Sounds nice, going to the summer
festival with a guy.
Oh, then do you guys want to come with us?
I'd feel better if you guys were there.
Are you an idiot?
Read the room.
But I see, I see. That's right.
The trial period is almost over,
so you guys would have to
decide pretty soon, huh?
Hey, what do you want
to do for the summer festival?
Oh, it's that time
of the year, isn't it?
The girls from Class D are all saying
we should all go together, and—
I'll go.
That was fast.
Oh, hey, Teach!
Yes, Ichimura-kun?
I'm going with Yoi-chan,
so can I be dismissed?
Seriously?! That's the
first I'm hearing of this!
It's the first time I'm saying it.
Wh-When did you guys decide this?!
Yesterday.
Yest—
Damn you! Damn you to hell!
Quit wishing ill on me.
Oh, hey, isn't your little
experiment almost over?
You still don't have an answer?
Well, there's no need to rush that.
Look at you, getting carried away.
Hey, you really okay saying that?
She might just get taken
by another man, y'know.
Huh?
The Prince has been looking
oddly cute lately.
That's true.
There's other guys who'd
be interested in her, too, yeah?
Besides, if one of you falls
in love with someone else,
the contract gets terminated, right?
Shouldn't you be takin' it
a little more seriously?
Just kiddin'!
I wonder...
Whose mouth is that ridiculous
claim coming from?
O-Ow, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Oh? It's you, Sentaro-kun!
It's the Romero Special!
I said I was kiddin'!
Sentaro, you got this'?!
No, I give up! I give up!
And, where's my sorry? Come on.
And the winner is Ichi!
Yoi, Oji-kun.
Business is a bit slow right now, so I'm
going to head out to get some things.
You two go ahead and eat.
Oh, okay.
Understood.
Thank you for the meal.
Whoa, that's good!
No matter how many times I eat
the curry here, it's delicious!
Dad would be happy to hear that.
You know, I partly took this
job for the free meals.
Free meals are a perk, for sure.
Hey. Yoi-san, that drink you have...
Oh, it's a lassi.
A lassi?
I wonder if it's sweet.
Do you like sweet things?
Oh, no, not particularly—
You've got a serious sweet tooth!
I didn't think I did,
but apparently I do.
Huh? What do you mean, "apparently"?
Nothing.
You know, you're an interesting
person, Yoi-san.
Um...
Are yukatas... something guys like?
Huh?
Oh, it's just... my friend is planning to
go to the summer festival with a guy.
It seems like she's having trouble
deciding whether to wear one that day...
But... she's concerned
about her boyish look
and whether it'd look good on her.
So she's wondering what to do.
Regardless of whether
it looks good or not,
I'd say I definitely would be happy.
Huh?
Knowing she went through all the trouble
to dress up just for you
would make any guy excited.
We're surprisingly simple like that.
Oh, I see.
Thank you very much.
Oh, I'll let her know that.
I'm glad I could be of help.
Is that right.
I see.
Um...
Are you planning on going with someone
to the summer festival, Yoi-san?
What...
I'm back!
W-Welcome back!
Oh, you guys finished eating?
Yes, it was delicious.
That took me by surprise...
Suddenly locking eyes with him when
he's so close is nerve-wrecking.
Oh, that's right.
I picked up some customers on the way.
Huh?
Ta-da, it's Ichimura-kun and the gang!
Hey, it's really a curry place.
Come on in and have lots to eat!
Curry! Curry!
Senpai?!
Why are you...
Sentaro said he really wanted curry.
Sorry, Prince.
I was opposed to it 'cause I knew
I'd get in trouble with you, but...
Hmm?
Huh? Did you always have this
handsome guy working here?
Huh?
H-Hey, please don't bother our part-timer.
Sorry about them.
Oh, no worries.
Hmm, a new part-timer, huh?
Hmm? What?
It's a shame, Ichi.
Such a fleeting love you had there.
Huh?! What're you guys talkin' about?
The Prince has been looking
oddly cute lately.
Let's make sure I got your order right.
A chicken, a beef, and a special, correct?
What is it?
Why are you staring
at my face like that?
Hmm? Oh, my bad, my bad.
I was just thinkin' about how
beautiful you are today.
Huh?!
H-Hey, Ichi, how do you say something
so forward with such ease?
Oh, come on. It's the truth, after all.
H-Hey, he's making me blush.
What is wrong with him?
Three new customers with
one serving each, please.
You got it.
Oh, Yoi-san, there's
something on your ear.
Where is it?
Oh, a little to the left.
Huh?
Uh, and a little down...
Um... Right here.
Sorry.
Huh? What is that?
Yogurt?
Oh!
The lassi!
That's embarrassing.
Oh, not at all.
I'm sorry.
Oops, sorry.
Seems like my hand slipped.
Ichi, you good?
Oh, no worries.
We'll wipe it up right away.
Yoi, get a rag.
Oh, right.
Are you all right?
Yeah, sorry about that.
Did it get on your clothes?
Nah.
It's a good thing it didn't
spill as much as I thought.
Yep.
I did it on purpose.
What?
Senpai, can we talk?
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Just what is going on here?
I could ban you from our store
for disruptive behavior, you know.
I'm very sorry. I won't do it again.
Look me in the eye
when you say it, please.
Jeez...
That newbie sure is handsome, isn't he?
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Wh-Why did you say that?
Oh, no reason.
I just happened to see you
two talking while I walked in.
You seemed awfully close, so I was
curious what you were talking about.
That doesn't have anything
to do with you, Senpai.
Is that so?
Actually, you're acting kind
of strange today, Senpai.
Not at all like yourself.
It feels like I'm back to the
time when I couldn't figure him out.
It's nothing.
I'm just jealous is all.
What?
I'm goin' inside.
Oh, Ichi, you're back.
Huh, where you goin'?
Gotta shit.
Huh?
Oh, the bathroom.
Damn it.
Pisses me off...
I'm just jealous is all.
What?!
What did he mean by that?
Oh, man. I'm stuffed.
Well, you ended up ordering
two servings' worth, Sentaro.
My bad.
I was the one who ended
up finishing most of it.
My bad.
So, you know—
After that, Senpai ate curry and
chatted as if nothing had happened.
But he still hasn't looked at me.
Hey, Yoi.
Yoi?!
Oh, that was a close one.
I-I'm so sorry! I'm so careless.
Oh, you're totally fine.
I just thought, it's rare to see you
spacing out like that during work.
Oh... I was just thinking about my exams.
Whoa, that just reminded me of mine, too.
If Senpai heard our conversation
just now, it'll be awkward.
All right, we should get goin' soon.
Yeah, you're right.
Thanks for the meal!
Uh, sorry, I'll be back.
Senpai!
U-Um...
Thank you... for dining with us.
Yep.
Later.
Uh, later, Prince!
Take care!
Huh? That seemed a little...
That was kinda cold, don't ya think?
What was?
The way you spoke to
the Prince on your way out.
You were all, like, "Yeah, bye."
Yeah, I can see that.
Nah, it wasn't like that.
Huh, could it be that our
Ichi is jealous?
Look at you! You actually
do have a cute side to ya!
Hey, keep it down, Sentaro.
Is that a problem?
N-No... It's not a problem.
Please select payment method
Cash
Credit Card
QR Payment
Point Payment
IC Card
Go Back
Call Clerk
Wha?! What was that?
A chill just ran up my spine!
Actually, I think it's the first
time I've ever seen Ichi angry.
Same.
It's like, even he gets jealous
and stuff sometimes, huh?
What?
What's wrong?
Sorry. I'm getting distracted
because you're here.
It feels like a parent
classroom observation day.
Stop making me laugh
Hey
Today after school, would
you like to go somewhere?
It feels like a parent
classroom observation day.
Stop making me laugh
Hey
Today after school, would
you like to go somewhere?
I'm sorry.
I have work today
Okay, got it
I'm just jealous is all.
Later.
It was all so sudden.
How was I supposed to respond to that?
I'm home.
Whoa! Gosh, it's dark!
Welcome home.
At least turn the light on, sheesh!
Where's Mom?
Night shift.
Oh yeah.
So is that new hire your boyfriend, Yoi?
Huh?
Oh, he's not?
His name is Oji, so I thought that's
where "Prince" came from.
Enough with the puns!
Aw, bummer. That's boring.
And, in all actuality, I'm not dating him.
Why aren't you guys dating?
He's kinda the type I can't fully trust.
He's so carefree and shifty,
he's hard to figure out.
If I were to compare him to an animal,
he'd be a cunning fox that tricks people.
What? He is a prince, right?
Besides, neither of us is entirely
sure about our feelings yet...
He tells me he loves me, but it's
always just about the way I look.
And this is a first for me, too, so
it's all a bit overwhelming, you know.
What?!
Who cares if it's just about looks?
And what's wrong with being smitten by
someone who has an interest in you?!
You need to learn to go with
the flow a little more.
Tell me, do you get the flutters
with anyone besides this guy?
Huh?
Besides... Senpai?
Well, it's good to be cautious
before you cross a stone bridge.
But hitting it too many times
may just break it, so be careful.
It's never crossed my mind before.
Hey, where did you put the measuring cup?
We're gonna make muffins, huh?
Whoa!
Yoi-chan!
How much flour were you supposed to sift?
What...
Oh!
You're right, sorry.
Ah, I'm sorry!
Oh, gosh, it's burnt!
It's rare to see you make so many
simple mistakes, Yoi-chan.
I was a little lost in thought.
Oh, what is it?
Is it about the festival next week?
Oh, right. The festival.
We're still going together... aren't we?
Well, I'm glad one of
them turned out pretty.
Why don't you take that to Senpai?
Might as well!
Go on, go on.
There's no way I'm taking it to him!
I said stop teasing me, okay?
Yeah...
I'll do that.
Um...
Do you know where I
could find Ichimura-senpai?
It's about the committee.
Oh, he got called to the staff room for
the incident during our lunch break.
What, the staff room?
Hey!
Oh, sorry, see ya.
Hey, was that a first-year?
She was so handsome that I freaked out.
What the?
I swear my inner feminine
side was, like, screaming.
Are you serious?
Forget flutters.
I didn't feel a single...
Hang on. What am I even doing?
That's just being rude.
Yoi-chan?
What are you doing?
Oh, um. I just happened to be passing by, and...
Hey!
That was a close one.
Are you hurt?
No... I'm fine.
Whoops.
Sorry.
It's okay... Thank you very much.
So, what are you doing here?
You got business on the second-year floor?
Uh, um...
Ichi!
How long's this gonna take?
I'm comin'!
Well, Imma go.
Oh, um...
Would you like to walk home together?
Give me a sec.
Sorry, guys, you go on ahead.
Huh? You sure?
All right!
See ya later!
Sure.
Let's go home.
Is there even anyone else...
who can make me feel this way?
Um, did you need to do
something in the staff room?
Oh, they found out I slipped out
during lunch to buy a beef bowl.
A beef... That'd definitely
get you in trouble.
I really thought I wouldn't get caught.
I used all sorts of secret shortcuts, too.
Come to think of it, he does come
out of strange places, doesn't he?
If only I were a wizard.
I could use a broom to zoom around,
or become invisible to sneak out.
Wouldn't it be faster to use magic
to make the beef bowl then?
You are a wizard, after all.
Tou​ché.
He didn't think of that?
Genius! Marvelous! Beautiful!
What does "beautiful" have
to do with it?
Huh... We're sort of having a
normal conversation, aren't we?
Um, this is totally off the subject,
but if you'd like, this is...
Who is even?!
Yes?!
Hello, Yoi-san? It's Oji.
Oji-kun?
Sorry, I couldn't get
a hold of the manager.
Could you let him know that my train's
delayed and I'm running a little late?
Oh, all right. Will do.
Thank you very much.
You guys exchanged numbers, huh?
Well, yeah. We work in shifts, so...
Uh-huh...
I don't like it.
Did you know that Mr. Handsome
clearly has a thing for you?
Huh? No, he doesn't.
We're just work buddies.
Guess it's fine, if you don't see it.
W-Well, you have a ton
of numbers from girls, Senpai.
Then I'll delete them all right now.
N-No, that's not the point!
You did it yesterday, too.
Could you please lay off the talk
about how jealous you are?
You might be used to
saying that stuff to girls,
but I have a hard time
responding to it...
I'm not used to it.
I'm not used to stuff like this either!
Forget it.
Um, Senpa—
Sorry.
Going home.
Well, it's good to be cautious
before you cross a stone bridge.
But hitting it too many
times may just break it.
I'm Just Jealous Is All
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis